[ Crowd Sounds ]
[ 人群讲话声 ]
[ Applause ]
[ 掌声 ]
&gt;&gt; Wow. It's very exciting to be
&gt;&gt; 哇哦 非常激动能够来到
here.
这里
I'm Gaurav.
我叫 Gaurav
And today we are going to
今天我们将会
discuss machine learning.
探讨一下机器学习
Machine learning is a very
机器学习是一项非常
powerful technology.
强大的技术
And together with the power of
再结合我们设备的性能
our devices, you can create some
你们能够创造出许多
really amazing experiences.
令人惊叹的体验
For example, you can do things
比如说 你可以
like real-time image recognition
进行实时图像识别
and content creation.
和内容创建
In the next 40 minutes, we are
在接下来的40分钟里 我们
going to tell you all about
将会向大家讲述
those experiences and how Apple
那些体验以及 Apple 如何
is making it easy for you to
方便快捷地
integrate machine learning in
将机器学习融入
your app.
你们的 App 中
In particular, we will be
具体来说 我们将
focusing on Core ML, our machine
专注于讨论 Core ML 和我们的机器
learning framework.
学习框架
At Apple, we are using machine
在 Apple 中 我们正在广泛地使用
learning extensively.
机器学习
In our photos app, we use it for
在我们的照片 App 中 我们使用它来做
people recognition, scene
人物识别
recognition.
场景识别
In our keyboard app, we use it
在我们的键盘 App 中 我们使用它
for the next word prediction,
来做输入预测
smart responses.
和智能回复
We use it even in our watch to
我们甚至在 Apple Watch 中使用它
do smart responses and
来做智能回复
handwriting recognition.
和手写输入识别
And I'm sure you guys also want
我很确信你们也同样希望
to create similar experiences in
创造出类似的体验
your app.
在你们自己的 App 中
For example, some of you might
比如说 你们中的一些人可能
like to do real-time image
想要做实时图像
recognition.
识别
In this way, you can tell your
这样的话 你们可以告诉用户
users, provide them more
为他们提供
contextual information about
他们所看到的 与场景更加相关的信息
they are seeing, for example
比如说
whether they are eating a hotdog
他们是不是
or not.
在吃热狗
[ Laughter ]
[ 笑声 ]
We want you to enable all of
我们希望你们能够启用
these great facility in your
这些非常棒的功能
app.
在你们的 App 里
And, hence, we are introducing
因此 我们推出
machine learning frameworks just
机器学习框架
for you guys to enable all the
让你们能够启用所有这些
awesome things.
酷炫的东西
You can clap.
你们该鼓掌了
[ Applause ]
[ 掌声 ]
But before we clap, we should
但是在我们鼓掌之前 我们应该
understand why do we even need
首先了解我们需要
machine learning in the first
机器学习
place?
的原因是什么
And when do you need machine
以及你们什么时候会用到
learning?
机器学习
So let's just say I'm a florist.
假设我是一名花匠
And all I want to show is all
我想展示的全都是
the images of roses in user's
玫瑰的图片
photo library.
在用户照片图库当中
This seems like a simple task,
这看起来是一件挺简单的事
so I can do some programming.
那么我要来编程
Perhaps, I'll start with the
可能我会从
color.
颜色入手
I say if the dominant color in
如果照片里的主色调
the picture is red maybe it's a
是红色 那这可能是一朵
rose.
玫瑰
The problem is there are many
问题在于 事实上
rose that are white in nature,
有许多玫瑰是白色的
white in color, or yellow in
或者是
color.
黄色的
So I will actually go forward
所以事实上我要更深入一些
and start describing the shape.
描述外形
And soon I will realize that
很快我就意识到
it's very difficult to write
这是非常困难的
even such a simple program
就算去写一个如此简单的程序
programmatically.
通过编程的方式
Hence, [inaudible] to machine
因此 我们需要机器学习
learning for our help.
来帮助我们
Rather than describing how a
与其去以编程的形式来描述
rose looks like
玫瑰是什么样的
programmatically, we will
我们会
describe a rose empirically.
通过我们的经验来描述一朵玫瑰
We will learn that
我们会去了解
representation of rose
玫瑰所代表的东西
empirically.
通过以观察经验为主的方式
Machine learning actually has
事实上机器学习
two steps.
有两步
One, training.
第一步 训练
So what you will do in this
那么在这一情况下你们要做什么
case, off-line you will collect
你们要在离线情况下收集
images of roses, lilies,
玫瑰 百合 向日葵的图片
sunflowers and label them.
并标记它们
You will run it past through a
然后你们要在一个
learning algorithm.
学习算法中运行它们
And you will get what we call as
之后你们会得到一个我们称之为
a model.
模型的东西
This model is an empirical
这个模型
representation of how a rose
代表着一朵玫瑰
look like.
是什么样子的
Almost all of this stuff happens
几乎所有这些事情
off-line.
都是在离线状态下完成的
And there is a big [inaudible]
有一个巨大的 [未听清]
on the Internet around training.
在互联网上 围绕着训练这个步骤
Training is a complex subject.
训练这一步骤算是一个复杂的问题
Now once you have the model, you
那么一旦你们有了这个模型
want to use this model.
你们就要使用这个模型
So what you will do, you will
那么你们要怎样做
take a picture of a rose, embed
拍一张玫瑰花的照片
this model in your app, you run
将这个模型嵌入你们的 App
it past through your model, and
将照片在模型中运行
you will get the label and the
你们就会得到标签
confidence.
以及可信度
This step is known as inference.
这一步被称为推断
Training is very complex, but
训练这一步是非常复杂的
inference is also getting very,
但在今天 推断也在变得
very challenging nowadays.
非常非常具有挑战性
For example, if you want to
比如说 如果你们想
describe a new, deep neural
以编程的方式描述出一个全新的
network programmatically in your
Deep Neural Network （深度神经网络） 在你们的代码中
code, you have to write
那你们将要写出
thousands of lines of code just
上千行的代码
to describe the network.
仅仅为了描述出这个网络
It can be [inaudible] tedious
这会是 [未听清] 很单调乏味的
and perhaps you can face your
很有可能你们会面临你们
biggest challenge in proving the
最大的挑战 就是当你们想证明
correctness of such a program.
这样一个程序的正确性的时候
Once you make sure that the
一旦你们确定
program is correct, you have to
这程序完全正确 你们还需要
make sure that you're getting
确认这一程序
the best performance possible.
尽可能有着最好的性能表现
Finally, you also have to make
最后 你还必须得确认
sure that there is energy
高能效
efficiency involved here.
也包括在内
These tasks can be very, very
这些工作是
challenging and can bog you down
非常非常具有挑战性的
completely.
同时也可以让你完全深陷其中
At Apple, we are using on-device
在 Apple 中 我们使用设备端的
machine learning for several
机器学习
years now.
已经有很多年了
And we have solved these
并且我们已经完成了
challenges.
这些挑战
We have faced these challenges
我们已经面对过这些挑战
and solved them.
并且成功完成了它们
And we really don't want you to
我们真的不希望
solve them.
由你们来面对这些难题
We will solve them for you.
我们会替你们搞定
We want you to focus only on the
我们希望你们只用专注于
experience.
体验即可
We will give you the
我们会直接给你们编译器
implementation, the best
尽可能是
implementation possible.
最好的编译器
And, hence, we are introducing
因此 我们为你们推出
machine learning frameworks for
机器学习框架
you in which case we take care
这样我们就可以来解决
of all the challenges, and you
所有的技术难题 由你们
take care of all the experience
来负责所有体验方面的问题
in your app.
在你们的 App 里
By doing so, we are going to
这样做的话 我们要
follow a layered approach.
遵从一种分层的形式
At the top is your app.
最上层的是你们的 App
We are going to introduce new
我们推出全新的
domain specific framework, in
Domain Specific Framework （特定领域框架）
particular, Vision.
具体来说是
The Vision framework will
Vision Framework （视觉框架）
actually allow you to do all the
使得你们能够做所有
tasks related to computer
与计算机视觉
vision.
相关的工作
The best part about computer
计算机视觉在 Vision Framework （视觉框架）中
vision of Vision framework is
最棒的部分
that you don't have to be a
就是你不需要是一名
configuration expert for using
视觉构造专家
Vision framework.
就可以使用 Vision Framework （视觉框架）
We are also enhancing our NLP
我们也在不断强化我们的
APIs to include more languages
NLP API （自然语言处理接口） 来容纳更多的语言
and more functionality.
和更多的功能
We are introducing a brand-new
我们推出一个全新的
framework called Core ML.
框架 它叫做 Core ML
This framework has an exhaustive
这一框架
support of machine learning
对机器学习算法有着全面的支持
algorithms, more deep learning
更有深度的学习机制
as well as a standard.
以及标准
And finally, all of these
那么最终 所有这些
frameworks are built on top of
框架都是建立在
Accelerate and Metal Performance
Accelerate and Metal Performance
Shaders.
Shaders 上的
To give you a sneak peak, we
我们可以通过 Vision Framework （视觉框架）
have Vision framework.
让大家先睹为快
Vision is our one-stop shop to
Vision 是我们的一站式商店
do all things related to
在其中可以做所有与
computer vision and images.
计算机视觉和图像有关的事
You can use it to do things like
你们可以用它来做像
object tracking or more modern
物体追踪或者
deep learning-based face
基于深度学习的
detection.
面部识别
There is a lot more to Vision
Vision Framework （视觉框架）
framework.
能做的还有很多
We are going to discuss Vision
我们会更加细化地讨论 Vision
in detail tomorrow afternoon.
在明天下午的时候
NLP, this is our one-stop shop
NLP 这是我们另一个一站式商店
to do the text processing.
用来进行文字处理
You can use it to do things like
你们可以使用它来做
language identification.
诸如语言鉴别之类的事
And we are also releasing Named
那么我们也会推出
Entity Recognition APIs.
Named Entity Recognition API （命名实体识别接口）
These APIs can actually tell you
这些 API 可以告诉你
in your text if it is a name of
在你的文字中这是否是一个
the location, people, and
地名 人名
organization.
或是组织机构名
We believe this will be very
我们相信这对于许多 App 开发者而言
powerful for many app developers
是非常强大的功能
so please check this out
所以请各位去更多的了解它
tomorrow more in the morning
在明天早上的
session on NLP.
有关 NLP 的研讨会中
Core ML, until now, we were
Core ML 直到现在
discussing domain specific
我们一直在讨论
framework.
Domain Specific Framework（特定领域框架）
Core ML is our machine learning
Core ML 是我们的
framework and is domain
机器学习框架
agnostic.
并且它是对领域不敏感的
It supports multiple kind of
它支持许多种
inputs such as images, text,
输入形式 例如图像 文字
dictionaries, raw numbers.
字典 原始数据
So you can do things like music
所以你可以做例如
tagging.
标记音乐之类的事
There's another interesting part
Core ML 还有一个有趣的地方
of our Core ML that it has the
就是
ability to deal with mixed
他有处理混合
input/output type.
输入输出类型的能力
So you can take an image and you
你可以拍一张照片
can get a text out.
然后得到一段文字
The best part about all these
这些框架最棒的部分
frameworks is that they can work
在于它们可以一起
together.
工作
So you take a text, you pass it
你可以写一段文字 然后使它
through your NLP, you get the
通过你的 NLP 之后你得到一个输出值
output, and you pass it through
接着你运行使它通过
Core ML and do things like
Core ML 来做出如
sentiment analysis.
情感分析之类的事
We are going to discuss it in
我们将会在关于 Core ML 的研讨会上
detail in our in-depth Core ML
更细化地探讨这些
session, how you do that exactly
如何进行操作
on Thursday.
上述研讨会将会在周四时举行
All of these frameworks are
所有这些框架
being powered by Accelerate and
都是由 Accelerate and MPS
MPS.
所驱动的
These are our engine.
这些就是我们的引擎
Now you can use Accelerate and
无论何时当你们需要某些
MPS whenever you need some kind
与数学相关的功能的时候
of math functionality.
你们可以使用 Accelerate and MPS
So it doesn't have to be
所以它不一定必须
necessarily related to machine
与机器学习
learning.
相关联
You can also use these
你们也可以
Accelerate and MPS when you are
在创造定制化的 ML 模型时
doing custom ML models.
使用 Accelerate and MPS
So if you are using a machine
所以当你们在使用
learning model, you might like
机器学习模型时
to use Accelerate and MPS.
你会想要用到 Accelerate and MPS
All these APIs run on user's
所有这些 API
device.
都是在用户设备上运行的
And they're very, very highly
并且它们都有非常
performing.
优秀的性能表现
And we work very hard to make
我们十分努力地钻研
sure you get the best
以确保你们能够得到最好的
performance possible.
性能表现
Now because they learn on user's
因为它们是在用户设备上进行学习的
device, there are advantages.
所以具有以下优势
First, user privacy.
首先 用户个人隐私
Your users will be happy to know
用户非常乐意知道
that you're not sending their
你并没有
personal messages, texts, and
发送他们的个人短信 文字
images to the server.
和图像到服务器上
Your users don't have to pay
你们的用户不需要花费额外的
extra data cost just to receive
数据流量 来接收这些
these -- just to send this data
不 来发送这些
to the server to get a
到服务器端以获得
prediction.
预测功能
You also don't have to actually
你们同样不用支付
give huge amount of money to
一大笔钱
server companies just to set up
给服务器公司 就为了
the servers and get a
建立服务器来获得
prediction.
预测的功能
Our devices are very, very
我们设备的
powerful.
性能非常非常的强大
You can do a lot here.
你们可以在设备上做许多事
And finally, your app is always
最后 你的 App 会保持
available.
可使用的状态
Let's just say your user goes to
让我们假设你们的用户去了
Yosemite in the wilderness where
约塞米蒂国家公园里的荒野
there is no network
到了一个没有
connectivity.
网络的地方
They can still use your app.
他们还是能够使用你们的 App
And this is very powerful.
这是非常强大的
However, perhaps one of the best
然而 也许你们能做的最棒的事之一
things you can do is real-time
就是
machine learning.
实时机器学习
Our devices are very powerful.
我们的设备性能非常强大
They can run modern deep neural
它们可以运行 Modern Deep Neural Network（现代深度神经网络）
networks such as ResNet 15
例如 ResNet 15
[inaudible].
[未听清 ]
You can use our devices to do
你们可以使用我们的设备来做
real-time image recognition.
实时图像识别
In these cases, you really don't
在这些场景下 你不会有
have [inaudible] to actually get
任何延迟就能够获得
the application.
实际应用
[ Applause ]
[ 掌声 ]
So for any latency sensitive
所以对于任何具有潜在敏感性的事物
things, you might like to do
你可能会使用
real-time image recognition.
实时图像识别
So just to recap here, we are
那么我在这里简要重述一下
releasing a series of machine
我们将会推出一系列的机器学习
learning frameworks.
框架
If your app is a vision-based
如果你的 App 是以视觉显示为主的
app, please use Vision
请务必使用
framework.
Vision Framework （视觉框架）
If your app is a text-based app,
如果你的 App 是基于文字的
please use NLP.
请使用 NLP
Now if you think that NLP and
那么如果你觉得 NLP 和 Vision Framework（视觉框架）
the Vision framework are not
都没有提供
providing the APIs you need, go
你所需要的 API
down on Core ML.
就直接去到 Core ML 层面
Core ML provides exhaustive
Core ML 可对
support of standard machine
标准机器学习
learning and deep learning
和深度学习算法
algorithms.
提供全面支持
And let's just say you are
假设你
[inaudible] your APIs machine
[未听清] 你的 API 机器
learning algorithms then you
学习算法 那么你
should use Accelerate and MPS.
应该去使用 Accelerate and MPS.
We are going to discuss all
在接下来的几天里 我们将会深入地探讨
these frameworks in detail in
这些框架
the next couple of days so you
所以你们
are [inaudible], but today let's
[未听清] 但是今天
just focus on Core ML.
让我们只关注于 Core ML.
And to do that, I'll invite my
接下来 我将邀请
friend and colleague, Michael.
我的朋友和同事 Micheal 上场
&gt;&gt; Thanks Gaurav.
&gt;&gt; 谢了 Gaurav
Hi everyone.
大家好
I'm so excited to talk about
我非常激动能够在这里介绍
Core ML and its role in helping
Core ML 以及它在帮助你们
you make a great app.
创造一款优秀的 App 时所扮演的角色
We're going to start out with a
我们的讨论将从
high level overview of Core MLs
高级别 Core ML 的主要目的概览
main goals.
开始
We'll then talk a little bit
之后我们会讨论一些
about models and how they're
关于模型的事项以及它们
represented.
是如果被表现出来的
And then we'll walk you through
随后我们会带大家了解一下
the typical development process
使用 Core ML 的
using Core ML.
典型的开发过程
So the Core ML framework is
Core ML 框架
available on macOS, iOS,
适用于 macOS iOS
watchOS, and tvOS.
watchOS 和 tvOS
But Core ML is more than just a
但 Core ML 不仅仅是
framework and a set of APIs.
一个框架和一大堆的 API
It's really a set of development
它实际上是一套开发工具
tools all designed around making
被设计用于
it as easy as possible to take a
尽可能地简化
machine learned model and
机器学习模型的创造
integrate it into your app.
并将其融入你们的 App
This will let you focus on the
这会让你们专注于
user experience you're trying to
你们希望实现的用户体验
enable rather than the
而不是
implementation details.
代码编译的细节方面
Core ML is simple to use, will
Core ML 使用非常简单
give you the performance you
它会提供给你所需要的性能表现
need while being compatible with
同时兼容
a wide variety of machine
多种
learning tools out there.
机器学习工具
Its simplicity comes from having
它的简约之处来自于
a Unified Inference API across
它统一标准的推断 API
all model types.
涵盖了所有类型的模型
Xcode integration will let you
与 Xcode 相融合让你们能够
interact with machine learned
与机器学习模型互动
models using the same software
通过
development practices you're all
你们早就非常熟练的
already experts in.
软件开发应用
It uses the inference engines
Apple 已经把
Apple is already shipping to
它使用的推断引擎销售给了
millions of customers in its
上百万顾客
apps and systems services now
的 App 和系统服务中
being made available to you via
现在你们也可以使用它了
Core ML.
通过 Core ML
And as mentioned, these are
如之前所说 它们
built on top of Metal and
是建立在 Metal and
Accelerate to make the best use
Accelerate 的上层
of hardware that your apps are
以求最大化得提升你的 App
being deployed on.
所依附的硬件的性能
Core ML is also designed to work
Core ML 也同样被设计工作于
in this rapidly evolving machine
这快速更迭的
learning ecosystem.
机器学习生态系统中
It defines a new public format
它定义了一个全新的公共格式
for describing models as well as
以描述模型
a set of tools that will allow
同时还有一套工具
you to convert the output of
使你能够将
popular training libraries into
Popular Training Libraries （普通训练库）的输出值转换
this format.
为这一格式
So that's Core ML in a nutshell.
简言之 这就是 Core ML
It's all about making it super
能够让
easy to get a learned model
你的 App 中融入学习模型的过程
integrated into your app.
变得极其简单
So let's talk a little bit more
让我们再多讨论一下
about these models.
这些模型
Since Core ML, a model is simply
因为 Core ML
a function.
一个模型就基本上是一项功能
Now the logic for this function
那么这项功能的逻辑
happens to be learned from data
恰好是从数据中学习而来
but just like any other
但就像其他任何功能一样
function, it takes in a set of
它接受一系列输入值
inputs and produces a set of
然后产出一系列
outputs.
输出值
In this case, shown on the
在这个情况下 如幻灯片所示
slide, we have a single input of
我们有一个单一的图像输入
an image and an output, perhaps
和一个输出值
telling you what type of flower
可能会告诉你什么种类的花
is present in it.
包含在其中
Now many of the use cases in
在许多使用场景中
which you may want to apply a
你也许想应用
machine learning model have some
在核心中有关键功能的
key function at its core.
机器学习模型
A common type of function is
一项常见的功能就是
performing some sort of
做出一种
classification.
分类
It's taking a set of inputs and
它接受一系列的输入值
assigning some categorical
并给它们指定
label.
一些分类标签
Take, for example, sentiment
比如说
analysis.
拿情感分析举例
Here, you may take in an English
你输入一句英文语句
sentence and output whether the
并输出
sentiment was positive or
这句话是积极的还是消极的
negative, here represented by an
然后这里
emoji.
由一个 emoji 代表
Now, in order to encode
那么为了编写
functions of this type, Core ML
这种类型的功能 Core ML
supports a wide variety of
支持种类繁多的
models.
模型
It has extensive support for
它对于神经网络有广泛的支持
neural networks both feedforward
包括前惯性
and recurrent neural networks
和周期性神经网络两种
with over 30 different layer
以及超过三十种不同的层级
types.
类型
It also supports tree ensembles,
它同样支持 Tree Ensembles （树集）
support vector machines, and
支持向量机
generalized linear models.
和广义线性模型
Now each of these model types
每一个类型的模型
are actually a large family of
事实上都是
models.
模型的大集合
And we could spend the rest of
我们可以利用这场研讨会
this session and the rest of
以及整场大会所剩余的时间
this conference just talking
来讨论
about any one of them, but don't
它们其中的一个
let that intimidate you.
但是请不要被吓到了
You do not need to be a machine
你不需要成为一个
learning expert to make use of
机器学习专家才能使用
these models.
这些模型
You continue to focus on the use
你只要继续专注于
case you're trying to enable and
这些你尽力想实现的使用场景
let Core ML handle those
让 Core ML 去处理那些
low-level details.
低级的细节即可
Core ML represents a model in a
Core ML 代表一个模型
single document.
在一个文件中
That is, sharing a model is just
也就是说 分享一个模型就像
like sharing a file.
分享一个文件
This document has the high level
这个文件有着高级信息
information you, as a developer,
是作为开发者的你
need to program against.
需要编程完成的
That is the functional
这就是功能
description, its inputs, types,
描述 它的输入 类型
and outputs as well as those
输出 以及那些
details that Core ML needs to
Core ML 为了执行功能
actually execute the function.
所需要的细节部分
For a neural network, this may
对于神经网络而言 这应该就是
be the structure of the neural
神经网络的结构
network along with its trained
加上它的
parameter.
训练参数
We encourage you to come to our
我们鼓励大家去
Thursday session to learn more
我们周四的研讨会来了解更多
about this format and the set of
关于这个格式
models it can encode.
和一系列它可以编码的模型
But maybe now in the back of
但是可能现在
your head you're starting to
你们会想
think well, where do I get these
我到哪里才能弄到这些
models?
模型
Where do models come from?
模型是哪里来的
Well, a great place to start is
那么 建议大家从这里开始
to visit our machine learning
查看我们的机器学习
landing page on
登场介绍页面
developer.apple.com.
在 developer.apple.com.
There you'll find a small
接着你们会找到一些
collection of task specific,
执行特定任务
ready to use models already in
立即可用的模型
the Core ML format.
已经是 Core ML 格式的了
We'll be expanding the set
我们会扩充这一套模型
overtime.
随着时间的推移
And we encourage you to explore.
同时我们鼓励大家不断探索
Give it a try.
尝试一下
This is a great way to get
这是一个很棒的途径
introduced to machine learning
去总体了解一下机器学习
in general and Core ML and how
和 Core ML 以及
it can be used in your app.
它们可以怎样被应用到你的 App 中
But we may not have all the
但是我们可能没有
models you need.
所有你们需要的模型
And for your application, you
为了让你们能够应用
may need to make some
你们可能需要基于现有的模型做一些
customization to an existing
定制
model or make a whole new model
或者从头开始
from scratch.
制作一个全新的模型
And for that, we encourage you
因此我们鼓励你
and your colleagues to tap into
和你的同事们利用好
the machine learning community.
机器学习社区
There is a thriving community
这是一个非常活跃
out there.
的社区
There are tons of libraries and
那里有无数的库和现成的
models already existing for you
模型可供你们
to start playing with.
使用
In addition, there are wonderful
另外 每周都会有非常棒的
online courses and new tutorials
线上教程和全新的课程
are popping up every week.
上线
You can do it.
你们可以做到的
There's great resources to
那里有非常棒的资源
learn.
可供学习
And I'm confident that all of
我有信心
you can get started.
你们都可以成功起步的
It's a wonderful time.
这是个美好的时代
But you'll see that most of
但你们会发现
these libraries are focused
大部分的库都是专注于
around training.
训练的
That is, it's a very important
因为 这是非常重要的一步
step but they'll spend a lot of
他们会花大量的
time making sure that you can
时间确保你们可以
train a great model.
训练出一个很棒的模型
What we want you to do is let
我们希望你们做的是
Core ML take you that last mile
让 Core ML 代替你们
from taking that machine learned
去获得那些机器学习模型
model and actually deploying it
并切实部署到
in your app.
你们的 App 上
So we're doing this by
所以我们推出 Core ML 工具
introducing the Core ML Tools
来做这些
Python package.
Python package
This is a Python package that is
这是一个 Python package
centered completely around
它完全集中于
taking the output of these
接受这些来自于机器学习库的
machine learning libraries and
输出值
getting them into the Core ML
并将它们转化为
format.
Core ML 格式
We'll be expanding these tools
随后我们会不断扩充这些工具
over time, but they're also
但同时
being made Open Source.
它们也是开源的
[ Applause ]
[ 掌声 ]
So what this means, if you don't
所以这意味着 就算你没有
find the converter you need
找到你需要的转换器
there, we're super confident you
我们非常相信
can already write your own.
你也已经可以自己写出一个了
All of the primitives are there
所有这些原始数据
ready for you to use.
都可以随时为你所用
Now I encourage you, again, to
我再次鼓励大家
visit us on Thursday to learn
来参加我们周四的研讨会
more about this Python package
了解更多关于 Python package 的信息
and how you can easily convert
以及你可以怎样简单地转换
models.
模型
OK. Now we have this model.
好的 现在我们有了这个模型
Let's talk about how we use it
让我们来讨论一下如果
in our apps.
在我们的 App 中使用它
So you're going to start with
那么你需要从
the machine learned model in
以 Core ML 为格式的
this Core ML format.
机器学习模型入手
You're going to simply add it to
你只需要将它加入到
your Xcode project.
你的 Xcode 的项目里
And Xcode will automatically
然后 Xcode 就会自动
recognize this model as a
将这个模型识别为
machine learned model, and it
机器学习模型
will generate an interface for
然后它会为你生成一个
you.
交互界面
That will give you a
它会给你一个
programmatic interface to this
这个模型的编程界面
model using data types and
使用的数据类型和
structures you're already
结构都是
familiar programming against.
你们编程时很熟悉的
You'll program using this
你们将会使用
interface and compile it into
这一交互界面并将它编译进
your app.
你们的 App
But in addition, the model
但除此之外 模型本身
itself will also get compiled
也会被编译
and bundled into your app.
并归入到你们的 App 中
That is, we'll take this format
也就是说 我们使用的这一格式
that's been optimized for
是已被优化过的
openness and compatibility and
变得更加开放及兼容
turn it into one that is
并且使它成为
optimized for run time on the
为了在设备上运行
device.
而优化的格式
To show you this in action, I'm
为了给你们展示这一操作
going to invite my friend and
我要邀请我的朋友
colleague, Lizi, to the stage.
兼同事 Lizi 到台上来
[ Applause ]
[ 掌声 ]
And I'm an engineer on the Core
我是 Core ML 团队
ML team.
的工程师
Today, let's take a look at how
今天 让我们来看一下
you can use Core ML to integrate
你们该如何使用 Core ML 将
machine learning into your
机器学习融入你们的
applications.
App
Now first some context.
首先设定一个背景
As much as I love machine
就像我喜爱机器
learning, I also love to garden.
学习一样 我同样喜欢园艺
And if you're anything like me,
如果你是像我一样的人
you may get really excited
每当你见到
whenever you come across a new
新品种的花时
kind of flower and instantly
相信你会非常激动并会马上
want to identify it.
就想认出它的种类
So we sought out to build an app
所以我们希望打造一款 App
that would take images of
可以获取
different types of flowers and
不同种类的花的图像
classify them by type.
并把它们按类型分类
But first, in order to do that,
但首先 要做到这一点
we needed a model.
我们需要一个模型
So we went ahead and we
所以我们进一步
collected many different images
收集了许多
of different types of flowers,
不同类型的花的图片
and we labeled each one.
并给每一个都做了标记
I then trained a neural network
之后我训练了一个神经网络分类器
classifier using an Open Source
通过使用一个开源的
machine learning tool and
机器学习工具
converted it into our Core ML
将其转换成了我们的 Core ML
format.
格式
So with this trained model and
有了这个训练出的模型
with this app shell of this
和这个花朵分类器的 App Shell （程序外壳）
flower classifier, let's take a
我们来看一下
look at how we can put the two
如果将这两者
together.
合二为一
So over in Xcode, you can see
在 Xcode 里 你可以看到
I'm currently running the flower
我正在运行花朵分类器
classifier app and nearing the
这个 App
display on my device.
就在我设备屏幕的边上
And what I can do is I can go
我可以做的就是
into the photos library and
进入到照片图库中
choose an image, but right now
选择一张图片 但现在
it doesn't currently predict
它还不能为输出结果
anything for the output.
做任何预测
It just displays this string.
它只显示出这一行而已
So if I move over to the
那么如果我去看
ViewController, what we see is
视频控制器 我们能看到的是
it has this caption method that
它有这样一个 Caption Method （说明方式）
currently just returns that
目前只会返回
blank string.
空白行
It doesn't actually do anything.
它实际上并没有做什么
Over here, I have this flower
在这里面 我有
classifier in the ML model
花朵分类器
format.
是以 ML 模型为格式的
And all I need to do is take it
我需要做的就是选中它
and drag it over into the
并将它拖拽到
project.
项目中
And we can see, as soon as I add
我们可以看到 我一把它加入进去
it, Xcode automatically
Xcode 就自动
recognizes this file format.
识别了这个文件格式
And it populates the name of the
显示出了模型的名字
model as well as what type it is
以及它的类型
underneath.
在这下面
We can see that the size is 41
我们可以看到文件大小是
megabytes and also other
41 兆字节 以及其它
information like the author,
信息例如作者
license, or description
许可或者描述
associated with it.
都一起显示出来
In the bottom, we can see the
在底部 我们可以看到
inputs and outputs that this
这个模型所承接的
model takes which, first is
输入和输出 首先就是
flower image, a type of image
花朵图像 它的类型是图像
that's ordered red, green, blue,
被划分为红色 绿色 蓝色
the following width and height.
以及宽度和高度
We can also see that it outputs
我们同样可以看到
a flower type as a string.
它将花朵类型输出为一行
So if give it an image of a
所以如果给它
rose, I would expect flower type
一张玫瑰的图片 我会想要花朵类型
to be rose.
显示玫瑰
There's also a dictionary full
这里同样存在一个词典
of probabilities for different
包含许多不同类型花朵
types of flowers.
的可能性
Now the first thing I want to do
我要做的第一件事
is I want to make sure that I
就是我要确保
add this to my app.
我把它加入到了我的 App
And you'll see that afterwards
之后你们会看到
this middle pane will show that
这中间的窗口会显示
the Swift generated source has
Swift Generated Source （生成源）
arrived in the application.
已经加入到了 App 中
What that means is we can
这意味着我们可以
actually use this generated code
真正地使用这生成的代码
to load the model and predict
来加载这一模型
against it.
并靠它来做出预测
To show you, let's go to the
为了给你们展示 我们看一下
ViewController.
视频控制器
The first thing I want to do is
我要做的第一件事是
define this flower model.
定义这些花朵模型
And to instantiate it, all I
为了将它实例化 我需要
need to do is use the name of a
做的就是使用
model class itself.
模型类本身的名字
We'll see that it's highlighted
我们会看到它被高亮的颜色标出
because it exists in the
因为它已经存在于
project.
这个项目中
Now next in the caption method,
在下一个 Caption Method （说明方式） 中
let's define a prediction.
我们来定义一个预测
And we'll actually use the
我们会使用
flower model and look inside.
这个花朵模型并查看它
We'll see using auto complete
我们会看到使用自动完成
that this prediction method is
这个预测方式是
available that takes a
可用的 并且它将
CVPixelBuffer as input.
CVPixelBuffer 作为输入值
We'll use that and pass the
我们要使用它并将
image directly to it.
图像直接传输给它
Now, instead of returning this
现在 我们可以取代
preset string, we can use the
这一预先设定的行 我们可以使用
prediction object and instead
预测物 同时取代之前的
return the flower type.
并返回出花朵类型
Now if I save, let's build and
现在如果我保存 我们就可以创建
run the app.
并运行这个 App
And what's happening while I do
我在做这件事的时候
this is the model itself is
这个模型本身
actually getting compiled and
正在被编译
bundled with the application.
并归入到 App 中
So if we go back to the device,
那么我们回到设备上看
if I go to my photos library, I
打开我的照片图库
can choose a rose on the second
选择一朵
row.
在第二排的玫瑰图片
And we can see it actually is
我们可以看到
able to display rose.
它能够显示出 玫瑰
[ Applause ]
[ 掌声 ]
We give it another one, maybe
我们再选一张
the sunflower on the third.
比如第三排的向日葵
It's also able to get this one.
它同样能够显示出来
Or even something a little bit
或者识别起来
more difficult like the passion
更加困难的 比如下面的
flower on the bottom, it can
西番莲
still do.
它还是可以识别出来
So to recap, we were just able
那么简要重述一下 我们可以
to drag a trained ML model into
将一个训练好的机器学习模型
Xcode and easily add it into our
拖拽到 Xcode 中  并将它十分简单地添加到
application with three lines of
App 中 只需要三行
code.
代码
And now we have a full neural
现在我们有一个完整的神经
network classifier running on
网络分类器
the device.
在设备上运行
But I have some other models
但我还有一些其他的模型
that we might want to try so
可能也想要尝试一下
let's go through this again.
那么让我们再做一次
You may have noticed there's
你们可能注意到了
also this FlowerSqueeze.
这也有一个叫 FlowerSqueeze 的模型
And the first thing I'll do is
那么首先我要做的
try to drag it in again.
就是再一次地拖拽它
And then I'll also add this one
然后我也要将它加入到
to the flower classifier, the
花朵分类器中
hello flowers target so that it
这个叫 Hello Flowers （你好花朵）的目标项目中
starts generating the Swift
然后在后台
source in the background.
开始生成 Swift 源
And we'll see, again if we zoom
我们会看到 如果我们再放大一些
in, that the name of this model
这个模型的名字
is different.
是不同的
It's called FlowerSqueeze but in
它叫做 FlowerSqueeze 但是在
the bottom the inputs and
底部 输入和
outputs are exactly the same.
输出是完全一样的
What this means is that if I go
这意味着如果
back into the ViewController,
我回到视频控制器中
instead of flower -- actually,
取代了花朵 干脆
let's delete flower classifier.
我们直接删除花朵分类器
We don't want that model
我们不再需要
anymore.
那个模型了
And in the ViewController,
在视频控制器中
instead of instantiating this
不再将这个实例化
one, we can use FlowerSqueeze.
我们来使用 FlowerSqueeze
And the really neat thing about
这个模型非常干净整洁的地方在于
this model is its size.
它的大小
So if we go back, this one is
我们返回 它的大小
only 5.4 megabytes, which is a
只有 5.4 兆字节
huge difference.
这是一个非常大的不同之处
Back in the device, we can go to
回到设备上 我们进入到
the photos library and choose
照片图库中并选择
another one like love in the
另一个 比如这朵雾中之爱
mist and see that this app is
可以看到这个 App
also able to classify this as
同样可以
well.
将它分类
Try another passion flower or
试一下另一朵西番莲或者
even a more difficult photo of a
一张更难识别的
rose on the side and it's still
边上这朵玫瑰的照片
able to predict correctly.
它仍然能够正确地预测出来
So to recap, we just saw that
再扼要重述一下 我们刚看到
we're able to run this neural
我们可以在设备上运行这个
network classifier on device
神经网络分类器
using Core ML, all with only a
通过使用 Core ML 这一切
couple lines of code.
都只用了仅仅几行代码而已
[ Applause ]
[ 掌声 ]
Now let's go back and recap what
现在我们来回顾一下
we just saw.
我们刚才都看到了什么
We saw that in Xcode, as soon as
我们看到在 Xcode 中  一旦
you drag an ML model that's been
你将一个训练过的机器学习模型拖拽进
trained into your application,
你的 App 中
you get this view that's
你会得到这个
populated that gives you
生成的界面 在下方提供给你
information such as the name of
例如模型名称
the model, the type that it is
和类型的信息
underneath, and also other
以及其他信息
information like the size or any
例如模型大小
other information the author put
或者任何其他
in.
作者加入进去的信息
You can also see in the bottom
在底部
that you get information such as
你们可以看到 例如这一模型的
the input and output of the
输入和输出的信息
model which is very helpful if
这是非常有帮助的
you're actually trying to use
当你想要
it.
使用它的时候
And once you add it to your app
一旦你将它加入到你的
target, you get generated code
App 中  你就会得到生成的代码
that you can use to load and use
你可以用来加载并使用
the model to predict.
这一模型来做出预测
We also saw in our application
我们也在 App 中看到
how simple it was to actually
使用它
use it.
是多么的简单
Again, even though the model was
再说一次 即便模型是
a neural network classifier, all
一个神经网络分类器
we needed to do to instantiate
我们将它实例化所需要做的
it was call the name of the
就是访问
file.
文件的名称
This means that the model type
这意味着模型类型
was completely abstracted so
是完全抽象的
whether it's a support vector
不论它是一个向量机
machine, a linear model, or a
一个一般线性模型
neural network, you all load
或者一个神经网络
them the exact same way.
你都可以以同样的方式加载它
We also noticed that the
我们还注意到
prediction method took a
预测方式使用到了一个
CVPixelBuffer.
CVPixelBuffer
It was strongly typed so you
它是一个强类型 所以你很清楚
know you'll be able to check
你要在
input errors at compile time
编辑的时候就检查输入错误
rather than at runtime.
而不是在运行的时候
But now let's take a deeper look
现在让我们来更深入的看一下
at the generated source that's
由 Xcode 创建的
being created by Xcode.
Generated Source （生成源）
Here, we see it defines three
在这里 我们看到它定义了三个
classes, first of which is the
层级 第一级是输入
input that defines the flower
将花朵图片
image as a CVPixelBuffer.
定义为一个 CVPixelBuffer
We then see the output with the
之后我们看到输出值
same two types that were listed
和两种相同的类型被列在
in the generated interface.
生成的交互界面中
And next, in the model class
接下来 在模型层级中
itself, we see the convenience
我们能看到
initializer that we use to
我们用来创造模型的
actually create the model and
便利构造器
the predict method as well.
以及预测方式
But also inside this generated
同时在 Generated Source （生成源）内
source, you have access to the
你可以接入
underlying model.
底层模型
So for more advanced use cases,
那么在更高级的使用场景中
you can use it as well to
你可以使用它
programmatically interact with
也可以以编程的形式
it.
与它互动
We take a look inside the
我们来看一下
MLModel class, we can see that
机器学习模型层级的内部 我们可以看到
there's a model description
有一个模型描述
which gives you access to
使你可以访问
anything you saw in the metadata
任何你在 Xcode
in Xcode.
元数据中看到的东西
There is also an additional
还有一个额外的
prediction method that takes
预测方式 它接受
protocol conforming input and
符合协议的输入
returns protocol conforming
并返回符合协议的输出
output giving you more
这给你
flexibility in how the input is
提供输入的方式
provided.
以更多的弹性空间
So we walked through the top
我们看过了
half of this development flow
这一开发流程的上半部分
and saw what happens when you
并看到了
drag a trained model into Xcode.
当你将一个训练过的模型拖拽进 Xcode 会发生什么
It's able to generate Swift
它可以生成 Swift 源
source that you can then use in
你可以在你的 App 里使用
your -- to use the model in your
在你的 App 里
application.
使用这一模型
The model itself, as we saw, is
如我们所见 这一模型本身
also compiled and bundled in
同样也被编译并归入
your app.
到你的 App 中
To elaborate on this step a bit
在这一步做一个更详细的说明
more, what we do, we first take
我们要做什么 首先
the model from its JSON form,
我们从模型的 JSON 形式中得到它
which is optimized for
这是优化过的
portability and ease of
为了更加便携和易于转化
conversion, and compile it so
并编译它
that it loads quickly on your
使它能在设备上快速加载
device when you initialize it.
当你启动它的时候
We also make sure that the model
我们还需要确认模型
is matched to the underlying
与底层推断引擎
inference engines that are
相连接
ultimately evaluating it on your
最终在你的设备上做出评估
device giving you optimized
并给你一个优化的预测结果
prediction when you need it.
当你需要的时候
And the last thing we saw in the
我们在演示中看到的最后一样东西
demo was we swapped out models.
就是我们换掉了模型
Mostly just to reduce the size
大多数时候都是为了缩减体积
but there are other reasons why
但是还有其他的原因
you might want to play around
为什么你可能会需要
with different ones.
使用别的模型
For example, accuracy or just to
比如说 为了精确性或者仅仅是
test out different types to see
为了测试出不同的类型
how they perform.
看它们表现如何
In summary, today we saw an
总的来说 今天我们了解了
overview of some of the machine
我们可用的一些
learning frameworks that we have
机器学习模型框架
available.
的概览
We also introduced Core ML, a
我们还推出了 Core ML
new framework for on-device
一个全新的框架
inference.
用于设备端的推断
And also we showed you the
我们也实际向你们展示了
development flow in action.
开发流程
For more information, make sure
需要更多信息的话
you check us out at
请到
developer.apple.com with our
developer.apple.com 查看
session number 703.
我们的研讨会序号是 703
And also, come visit some of the
同时 周四可以参加一些
related sessions such as Vision
的相关研讨会进行深入了解 例如 Vision
and NLP and Core ML in depth on
和 NLP 以及 Core ML
Thursday if you want to see some
如果你们想了解
more use cases of how you can
更多 Core ML 的使用场景
use Core ML or how to actually
或者如何
convert models into the Core ML
将模型转换为 Core ML
format.
格式
Thank you and enjoy the rest of
感谢各位
the conference.
并请期待大会接下来的日程